I think there's also sometimes like in coverage of it, a little bit of a backwards view in
my opinion, which is like the fact that PayPal and Stripe getting involved in stablecoins
is so good for the stablecoin industry.
But in reality, it's like these guys are going to get disrupted, they have this massive
legacy tech stack, and they need this technology to stay competitive.
Welcome to the Defiant Podcast, I'm your host Vinny, and today we're talking to Megan
Knapp, a co-founder and CEO of Franklin, a crypto-first payroll company.
Before that, she was VP of Finance at Cyrotonan, a Web3 marketing firm, and yeah, you've been
working in accounting in the crypto space for I guess the better part of 10 years now,
right?
Almost.
What about ages?
No, it makes you wise and experienced.
Yeah, it's been a minute.
Yeah, so I'd love to talk about your background in accounting.
It's one of those, you know, less glamorous parts of what makes the world go round.
Can you share a little bit about your early experiences in crypto and how that intersected
with your work in accounting, and how that all eventually led to the creation of Franklin?
Yeah, for sure.
So right out of school, I got a job working on Wall Street in a back office doing the
very kind of like office space grunt work that I think a lot of people think about when
they think about accounting.
Paper cushion?
Yeah, pushing papers around, manually confirming wires with the bank.
And Hurricane Sandy hit New York, actually, we, like me and another person in the department
had to actually go in, like I walked from my apartment in Queens downtown to run payroll
for the company.
You got your steps in?
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah.
I mean, you know, if it wasn't clear that and something needed to change, like, yeah.
So I worked as an accountant for about five years.
I was going to Baruch to get my MBA at night, and learned about Ethereum actually in business
school, which was, yeah, random I had a like very progressive forward thinking professor.
Was it part of the curriculum or just it came out in conversation?
It was so Nate Popper, who's a New York Times journalist, I think had just come out with
his book Digital Gold, and he came and gave a lecture to our class.
And kind of simultaneously, I had uncovered this, like, multi-million dollar accounting
fraud happening at the company that I was working at.
And it was just this weird confluence of a lot of things happening at the same time.
And I was like, Ethereum is the solution for corporate greed, and got really excited about
it.
I like rage quit my job.
I was, I was like, this is really edible.
Yeah.
I got a job working at consensus, and I was basically like, I am an accountant, but I'll
do anything.
And that's kind of the first few steps I took into crypto, that was some 2016.
So there was nobody doing crypto accounting for the most part then.
So yeah, I think there are a lot of things that led to the genesis of Franklin.
But that's the kind of base of like having this kind of like traditional skill set and
yeah, jumping into emerging markets.
So yeah, and so you've built back office systems within Web3.
Can you tell us about some of the lesser known challenges in doing that?
Yeah, I mean, it's changed so much over like even just the last two years before I think
like there was a big problem with like data availability.
And so that in a lot of ways has been solved where you can like find human readable information
about transactions on chain.
There's so many subledgers out there.
So I think that that's been really helpful.
Something that I was struggling with when I was running finance at serotonin was just
figuring out how do we have real world bills.
We are getting in revenue in crypto.
We need to pay people out in cash or crypto.
And so figuring out like how to like merge these two worlds like there are very few companies
that can really just totally operate on chain.
And so yeah, prototype Franklin within serotonin thinking about like, okay, let's see if we
can streamline all of these inflows and outflows and it worked great.
And there really wasn't anything else going on in the market at the time.
So that's how it started.
And like, how do you approach, you know, the volatility of crypto because like I'm thinking
about, you know, payroll with, for example, Ethereum, which just a couple months ago was
worth a lot less and six months ago, a lot more, right?
So how do you kind of like deal with that volatility when you're dealing with bills and
payroll that that's going to be probably USD versus crypto.
Yeah.
I mean, I think like there, yeah, I mean, it depends a little bit on like where you are
thinking about in the financial stack with payroll and like, yeah, like bill pay in general,
like there are a lot of regulations, like there are a lot of labor laws in the United
States about how people can be paid.
And it actually kind of emanates back to like Appalachia, where people were getting like
who worked for coal mining companies were getting paid in like companies certificates.
But it meant that they could never actually like leave their town.
They could never get out from grapes of wrath.
Yeah.
After that, yeah, there are a bunch of like state labor laws sort of like came about.
So, and they actually apply to crypto now as well.
So if you are working for a company and you're an employee in the United States, you can't
legally just be paid in that token, you have to be paid in a fiat equivalent currency.
And so taking a look at some of like the rules that we know exist was kind of like one of
the first things we did.
And when we, yeah, launching Franklin, we offered a bunch of different currencies.
We had a couple companies that used wrapped Bitcoin or wrapped it to pay out bonuses.
But most companies and most of our customers today still just use stablecoins.
Yeah.
Going off of that, I noticed that you that Franklin often works with ERC 20 tokens like
wrapped Bitcoin or stablecoins.
Was there a reason you wanted to work with those instead of a native token like Bitcoin
Ethereum Solana?
Yeah.
It's because we're smart contract based.
So just ERC 20s work with smart contracts.
We're also EVM based.
So yeah, from a technical perspective, that was the reason why path of least resistance.
Path of least resistance, but also it's like a really beautiful technical solution to something
that in the trad by world is like really patched together like super manual and a smart contract
automates a lot of that processing logic.
So that's kind of the genesis for it.
The coders in our audience are going to be really, really happy with that take.
So in a 2022 coin desk article, you highlighted how intermediaries like payday lenders and
check cashers cost Americans $15 billion annually, which is kind of a lot.
Yeah, it's a lot.
So given crypto's focus on getting rid of intermediaries, something we're very hyped
on, how could eliminating these middlemen positively impact employees?
Yeah, for sure.
There's a lot of ways.
And so one of the innovations at Franklin is actually it's like a self custodial payroll
platform.
So we're actually never taking custody of our customer's funds.
It's literally just a peer to peer transaction that happens on chain, which is cool.
That is not like a paradigm that exists in trad by at all.
There's also just like the power of stable coins.
There's a lot of upside to them.
But one of them is that you can just move money a lot faster.
That makes moving money a lot cheaper.
So we could think about like the different ways that businesses will start having to incentivize
their teams going forward when you have this new paradigm that's a lot cheaper to use.
There are some companies that use programs called Earned Wage Access, where it's supposed
to be like a perk where you can claim your paycheck a little bit early.
But it's actually sort of these like complex loan agreements.
And it's a modern payday lending type situation.
And so our theory is just like we can just pay it out faster.
You can hold on to your cash for longer and it's a better experience for everybody.
Eliminate the T plus three.
Yeah.
So many crypto companies are remote first and many of them have employees all around the
world, which we love, you know, it's more decentralized, more cool, more global.
But of course that can create some friction when we're talking about payroll.
So can you tell us more about how crypto first payroll infrastructure can support employers
and employees beyond the, you know, the obvious, you know, cross-border payments that stable
coins make way easier?
Yeah.
I mean, I think that it's interesting to see like how employment trends have changed over
the last like five years or so serotonin by a company that I was running finance at,
where I started Franklin started during the pandemic and it was a hundred percent remote.
Like they still don't have an office, I think.
And being able, I think like when you are running an international business, and this
is, sorry, I meant to say like a trend that other businesses have taken up as well, like
it is much more in vogue to hire globally now than it ever was before.
One good outcome of the pandemic.
Yeah.
One good outcome.
Exactly.
Right.
Yeah.
And I think that having a global team, you almost in the past had to have a bunch of local
infrastructure in every jurisdiction where you had people.
You still now have to comply with obviously like labor laws for wherever people are.
But yeah, operating on Shane, you just have one network to deal with instead of a bunch
of different banks, a bunch of different FX providers, things like that.
So simplicity.
Yeah.
Beautiful thing.
You've also stated that quote payroll is one of the fundamental building blocks for
the health and wealth of society.
Can you elaborate a little bit on that?
Yeah.
For sure.
At least in the United States, all of our social services boil down to a paycheck.
If you have to pay child support, or if you have to have your wages garnished, that flows
through to a paycheck, you know, our health insurance, all of that stuff.
Social security.
It's a really complex data problem, and it is, there are lots of examples of these kinds
of industries, but it is highly monopolized by the largest players.
Shocking.
Yeah.
Right.
So for us, when I was starting Franklin, it was actually really hard to figure out like
how do you actually calculate a paycheck?
So the tax code is open source, but it's actually not available anywhere.
Like there's no central repo for it.
And that was one of the first problems.
One of the first problems we had to think about how to solve.
So, you know, there are two large companies that basically have a tax database that you
can all payroll companies purchase.
And so for us, being able to move money faster, we want to be able to have more real-time
information, and so building our own tax calculator is one of the first things that we had to
do.
But yeah, it's the basis of society, Medicare, all of our social services, and it all boils
down to a paycheck.
Yeah.
That's fascinating.
Obviously, money rules the world.
So I was thinking in that context, but yeah, whenever you're thinking about, you know, how
we support one another, paying taxes and all that, like, yeah, it can't get complicated.
Yeah, yeah.
It's the ultimate community tool.
So.
Right.
The PR Genius is a top crypto PR and growth marketing agency, helping brands globally
with expert PR and strategic growth marketing.
They've worked with 300 plus projects like movement labs and IO.net.
Unlike traditional agencies, they charge only on performance.
Their services include earned PR opportunities and marketing services to help boost wallet
holders and organic ex followers.
Learn more at www.theprgenius.com.
So let's talk a little bit more about stable coins.
There are, of course, you know, one of the biggest, you know, trends in the news right
now as far as mainstream coverage of crypto.
Yeah.
And a lot of that is because of certain bills getting passed, not passed.
So let's talk a little bit about the Genius bill.
What are your thoughts on this bill and its potential implications?
Yeah.
I mean, if I zoom out and just thinking about it as an American citizen, it's kind of interesting
that crypto is the only kind of like bipartisan issue going through Congress right now.
Specifically, the Genius Act, I think, is a net positive for the industry.
We have generally had to rely on stable coin issuers being trustworthy.
And you know, the industry has come up with some standards or pressure, peer pressure,
to have some level of disclosure in stable coin reserves.
And so the Genius Act really makes it, you know, sets a standard for the kinds of disclosures
and audit requirements for issuers and also kind of gives a permission structure for trad
five financial institutions to start playing in the stable coin space.
So I think overall, it's a net positive.
We'll see what happens in its final form and how, yeah, how it might interact with some
of the other legislation that's also, you know, moving forward.
Net positive, I would say.
I think stable coins are like having a moment and hopefully it continues.
So it's going to be like hot stable coin summer.
Yeah.
Somebody should meme that.
Like, started here.
So one of the Genius Bill's requirements is for firms to hold a reserve of assets that
is equal to the value of issued stable coins.
I can't help but point out that banks are not held to the same standard.
Do you think that is a good thing?
Do you think it's, you know, a hindrance?
What's your take?
Yeah.
I mean, I think it's kind of almost just saying the obvious in some ways where, yeah, like
in tradfi, we have fractional reserve banking where banks can lend out a certain percent
of their balance sheet.
And that's, you know, how our money supply grows.
You know, I think like, I think a lot about maker Dow from like back in the day and how
their protocol actually evolves from having a single source of collateral and then having
multiple sources of collateral.
This kind of requirement is sort of, yeah, like drawing on some of the evolution from
like the maker Dow protocol days, I think.
But I think it's, you know, good for consumer protection.
It's good for US dollar global dominance.
There will be an increase in desire for T bills and things like that.
So if you care about that stuff, that's, you know, it's not positive.
I think it's good for the end consumer as well.
Yeah.
And seeing a lot of work in the crypto sphere that's talking about like benchmark rates
on chain.
Now we're talking about stable coins being more widespread, you know, stripe and PayPal
or both utilizing stable coins.
So do you think that these kinds of assets within the crypto realm are going to kind
of be that gateway for more traditional investors and maybe, you know, normies who they hear
about crypto and they're like, what?
Yeah.
I mean, I think like a lot of the crypto industry right now, there's just like a lot
of good vibes around some of these bigger brand names getting involved in stable coin
tech.
One thing that I think we should be careful about as an industry and as, you know, people
who operate on chain and operate in this space is sort of like capture by these bigger sort
of like payments players or even like government players where if you look at the current iteration
of the stripe stable coin products, it's like extremely expensive to use.
Like we looked at it like maybe we integrated at Franklin and it's insanely expensive to
use.
Really?
Yeah.
And yeah, it's like kind of like, well, you know, maybe prices, more price compression
will happen as more players get involved, but you know, if Visa, you know, just start,
we don't want stable coins to all be sitting on it, the Visa rails, you know, the innovation
behind this technology is that it is peer to peer.
And it should stay that way.
And if stripe and PayPal want to come in and participate, they're welcome.
But I think it's something to be wary of a little bit like you can come to the party,
but don't bogart the party.
Yeah.
Exactly.
I think there's also sometimes like in coverage of it, a little bit of a backwards view in
my opinion, which is like the fact that PayPal and Stripe getting involved in stable coins
is so good for the stable coin industry.
But in reality, it's like these guys are going to get disrupted that they have this
massive legacy tech stack and they need this technology to stay competitive.
And so that's kind of the angle that I approach it from.
It's like, yeah, took you long enough.
So yeah.
Get 20% APY on ETH with the high growth vault by KELP in one click.
High gain uses blue chip DeFi strategies with restaked ETH across AVE, PENDLE, USUAL,
and ELEXER, managed by strategy pros, ultra yield and upshift to deliver highest rewards
on ETH.
All in just one click, deposit your ETH, receive high gain ETH, and stay liquid in
DeFi.
Trade or use high gain ETH on platforms like PENDLE and Balancer while still stacking
rewards.
Follow along these steps to get started.
Some critics of the Genius Bill, including our fave Elizabeth Warren, our favorite hater
Elizabeth Warren, they've called the Genius Bill insufficient.
And she's even gone to say no bill would be better than a weak one.
Do you agree or disagree with this perspective?
Yeah, philosophically, a weak bill is not great.
I think that a lot of US politics, you're talking about one subject, but you're really
talking about something else.
And so I read a bunch of her comments, she is concerned about the Trump Organization
getting involved in crypto with issues around self-dealing, and my understanding is trying
to hold this bill a little bit to try and create accountability elsewhere.
It's a strategy, I don't like it as somebody who works in the stablecoin space, but I think
this kind of discourse is important to have.
I think it's an okay perspective to bring up, but ultimately the US has got to kind of
get moving on crypto.
We are very far behind in terms of creating a sane regulatory regime for startups, for
businesses.
So let's get it moving.
Well, and this lack of regulation is hurting people.
I always wonder how much of this is part of their game to make crypto look bad because
we don't have regulation for how the organizations should be set up, and that's how you get
an FTX collapse.
That's how we get all of these headlines that make us look like we're an industry of scammers.
How do we approach regulation on that way?
No, I think that's a really good point.
This will throw ignorance or not wanting to take it as a serious issue has caused a lot
of harm like FTX being a massive example of that.
There's some level of the US has the most sophisticated capital markets infrastructure
in the world, and moving slowly is a feature and a bug, and there's also some level of
you don't want regulators or legislators to get so far ahead of the ball where the technology
is evolving so quickly, I'm of the view like having audit requirements and disclosures.
Those are good things.
Let's mandate them.
And if there's something else that we need to do secondary to that, pass another bill.
The fact that Congress is just not going to do your job.
That's what I would say is some rules are better than no rules.
And let's just get it out there.
I think that a lot of the stuff that's in the Genius Act is common industry practice,
and so let's just put the stamp on it and keep going.
It's so funny to me when it's like, "Yeah, of course you should have some guardrails
in place."
Yeah.
I think crypto is sometimes split down the middle when it comes to the people who are
pro-regulation for everything we're discussing, then the people who are maybe anti-regulation
because regulation can stifle growth.
Yeah.
So crypto being literally a global thing, it seems like they have to be really smart
about just how are stablecoins specifically going to benefit or be bad for the American
people?
Yeah.
And I think that should be the main driver between the regulation versus these conversations
around whether the president is going to benefit or not.
I feel like the attention should be on the American people, not on an individual.
I think the thing that scares me about crypto in the United States is that it is becoming
more of a political issue and really it is not a political technology.
It is meant to really operate separately from governments.
In spite of government, Bitcoin was born out of the 2008 financial crisis.
And so there's some reality here where it's like, "I'm a U.S. citizen, I want to service
U.S. businesses, I want to follow the rules, but I want to not have so much intervention
where you're hamstrung from moving forward or from offering a good service."
I think that in the past couple of years, the biggest winners in the crypto industry
for a large part have been law firms.
You get your venture funding in and then spend a lot of time with lawyers trying to figure
out corporate structuring risk management policies and ultimately, there has not been
a clear path for a lot of founders, for a lot of people who want to operate on chain,
up until now.
I think it's generally good, but arm's length, it'll be a win if we get it done, I think.
Yeah, I love that you brought up lawyers because I have found that when you're talking to
people in crypto and specifically in DeFi, it starts to feel like you are interviewing
a legal team.
You know what I mean?
It's like they're clearly saying whatever they're allowed to say and not a word over
it.
And I mean, do you think that's just because of fear of the SEC or just the government
getting mad at them retroactively?
Because that's something I think a lot of people don't see.
Because of the lack of regulation, you might see a form of insider trading or a form of
these nefarious activities, but because it's not in the code, it's not technically illegal.
But people are still very careful about what they're going to say.
Sure.
Yeah, I mean, I think there's some level of discipline that great founders have around
sticking to talking points.
Yeah, I think, but yeah, I mean, there's a lot of fear.
I think like when I was starting at Franklin three years ago, the idea that we were going
to launch in the United States was I feel like some of our early investors were kind
of like, yeah, she's crazy.
Let's try it.
Like going to market in the US like in a very highly like regulated market is insane.
Right.
But you know, in some ways like there, because there were more rules for like around labor
regulations, it's almost easier because we have some framework already to try and operate
in.
But yeah, the lawyers, I think do a good job of scaring people and, you know, it's necessary.
I'm subject to it too.
Like my lawyers like a great friend.
So shout out Teddy, but yeah, totally.
So there are a lot of stablecoins out there and more and more coming out each day.
Even earlier this year, we have the Trump backed crypto firm world liberty financial launching
USD one.
And I know that stablecoin is probably part of what Elizabeth Warren and other Democrats
are thinking about when they're talking about wanting to stop Trump from, you know, benefiting
financially from stablecoin legislation.
But with so many options out there, how do you decide which ones to utilize both on a
personal level and with your business?
Yeah.
Well, the position of Franklin is like, we're never prescriptive to our customers about
like what assets they should use.
We have some limitations like we won't transmit or help transmit securities because we're
not a licensed broker dealer.
But for the most part, it's kind of, you know, the assets that you want to be using.
You can use them, check a couple boxes to make sure it's legal, go for it.
You know, personally, I think like there are a lot of things to consider and there are
going to be way more in the very near future as more institutions start playing in the space.
So like Santander, for example, announced, I think today that they were launching their
own stablecoin.
Like, I think we'll see that kind of playbook play out from a lot of different banks.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
I'm so dystopian to me for some reason.
I can't imagine why.
It's going to be weird.
It's going to be so weird.
I would love, you know, dollar sign, JPM stablecoin, I mean, they had JPM coin.
So which, you know, these like interbank settlement processes are so complex like this.
And I used to, I had a moment working in equities brokerage, like being able to, yeah, settle
transactions between institutions, like a blockchain, a public blockchain is a perfect
solution to these kinds of things.
But yeah, the vibes are going to be weird.
Like, it's also weird to me, like the Van Eck Twitter handle is like very de-gen.
And I'm like, who are you guys like, what, what, you know, who did what intern did you
hire?
Yeah, exactly.
Exactly.
So I think we'll, yeah, we'll see more of it.
You know, personally, I like assets that are not like, yeah, within a closed network.
So, you know, I, it's not really around as much anymore.
But like make or doubt, like those were, I think we'll all look back as an industry and
be like single collateral die, the multicolateral die upgrade, like that was maybe the coolest
thing that crypto has ever produced.
I'd love to hear more on that.
What made it so cool for you?
Yeah, I think it's just this idea that it could operate autonomously on chain as just
like, you know, I think crypto itself, like at a technology level is like pretty simple
tech, you know?
It aims to be, right?
Yeah, like smart contracts, right?
If then statements, like it's not, it's not like quantum, you know, or something like
that.
And just like being able to have that kind of like application use case to be able to
create money from your own money is just like genius, like, oh, so cool.
Yeah.
And I think it actually makes those concepts a little more accessible to people because,
you know, it's really interesting working in DeFi and getting to see the convergence
of traditional finance and how to enhance it or make it more available to the public
through blockchain technology.
And so I'll be curious to see how stable coins and how, you know, collateralized debt
can like really bring new wealth to people who don't work in the banking industry or
who don't have that expertise.
Yeah.
Yeah, for sure.
And I think that like, you know, this kind of like scarcity is really like there are people
in areas of the world that don't have access to traditional financial services that do
use this.
Like if you walk around when a sire is right, like a lot of you can pay out a lot of point
of sale systems using stable coins on Tron as an example.
And that's been, you know, if there are other examples of that and it's almost like here
where we have very sophisticated financial infrastructure, it is so slow to adopt.
But yeah, it's going to be wild.
Oh, that's a great point. Yeah, places that are still developing might just skip all the
stuff that we've been dealing with for the last few decades and go straight to.
Yeah.
A hundred more coins.
A hundred percent.
Why not?
Yeah, yeah.
Skip the line.
Goat network is the first sustainable BTC yield chain powered by decentralized sequencers
using multi-coin POS.
Goat's mission is to transform BTC and Doge from passive holdings into active yield generating
assets through a one-of-a-kind economic model that tokenizes sequencer revenues, unlocking
the full potential of BTC-Fi and meme-fi in a way that's never been done before, and
creating new yield opportunities for Bitcoin and Dogecoin holders.
Supply BTC or Doge earn BTC in perpetuity.
Let's start it through our user rewards onboarding portal, onepiece.goat.network.
A lot of the time when we think about crypto in places like Latin America or Africa, we
think about the ability to use an asset like Bitcoin as a store of value against something
like the Argentine peso, which can drop 80% in value overnight and we've seen this happen
in recent years, so do you think stablecoins are a better asset for these more developing
economies versus something like Bitcoin or Ethereum?
Yeah, I mean, I think a couple things about that.
One, I think of Paul Brody, who runs the global blockchain business at Ernst & Young.
He says Bitcoin is the asset and Ethereum is the platform, and he's trying to draw this
distinction of like, yes, Bitcoin is store value, I think the narrative around it being
digital gold is like, it trades closer to gold now than it does other assets.
Yeah, I saw that on the news and I was like, well, digital gold, I guess we have.
Yeah, yeah, by gold.
The other thing I think is like, a stablecoin is stable to what, you know, like we, stablecoins
are largely an orchestration of the US dollar right now, and so if you are pegging a stablecoin
to a currency that is volatile, that stablecoin will still have, you know, the same, it's
really just a layer of, you know, whatever fiat you're dealing with.
And so, you know, to me it's kind of like, you know, we can actually, not that we should,
you know, get the US dollar into more areas of the global economy, like I think it's going
to really cement like US monetary policy or like monetary, yeah, dollar dominance.
Yeah.
Interesting.
I've definitely seen conflict with the US government and something like Bitcoin because
Bitcoin is kind of positioned itself to be anti-USD, right, to be not working together,
but like something you want to have instead of.
Do you see stablecoins kind of flipping that script and maybe being something that the
government might be more welcoming to because it is potentially going to share that dominance
of USD throughout the world?
Yeah.
I mean, well, on the Bitcoin point, I think it's so weird, this industry in so many ways
where like a lot of people lauded the Bitcoin ETFs where it's like, okay, we're putting
Bitcoin on traditional like equities rails so that more asset managers can get exposure
to it.
And it's like, you know, ETFs on Bitcoin would be cool or ETFs on, you know, another like
chain like theory, like that would be real innovation, you know, and so like let's not
lose the plot, I think, to your point.
Yeah, we may not have a political ideology, but there is an ideology there.
Yeah, exactly.
So I think, yeah, stablecoins really are, yes, a kind of an antithesis to that Bitcoin
value prop, but maybe it's a Trojan horse, yeah, it could be, right, and technically,
you know, like the Fed and like the issuer of like monetary policy in the United States
is separate from like the elected government, right, but and like hopefully it stays that
way.
Yeah, you know, if I were a government leader, you know, having assets on a public blockchain
is a great tool for power.
And it's a little scary, like I think that's another thing that we should all be aware
of is like you can see everything happening on chain.
You can very easily exclude people or, you know, like Blacklist them off.
So you know, should a government like take up issuing stablecoins, sure, it's a great
idea for a government like, is it a great idea for its population?
Like, maybe not, whoa, careful, we're going to start giving the Trump administration some
ideas.
I'm sure there's no new new ideas here, but yeah, yeah, no, it's it's really fascinating
to see what's happening.
And I didn't really, I didn't see stablecoins as being the thing that would get us into
these conversations and having, you know, the words crypto coming out of so many politicians
mouths.
Yeah.
Are there any other pieces of legislation that you're kind of hoping will come out of this
or come next?
There is something that I'm kind of hoping for, it's not exactly related, it's not at
all related to stablecoins, but the SEC has rules around accredited investors that I think
are just so wack, I mean, to change where basically people who are not already rich cannot participate
in certain kinds of markets and get access to certain kinds of investments.
Yeah.
And the buy-in is crazy, right?
It's like you have to make $200,000 a year for three years in a row.
And or have a million dollars in the bank.
Yeah.
It's like, you know, definitely working on that.
Yeah, right.
Like, but yeah, don't have enough Bitcoin to be investing in anything.
Right.
And also to get an accreditation, like a lot of these evaluators like still won't touch
crypto and stuff like that.
So you have people who have, yeah, like crazy crypto network that like can't get, still can't
get that kind of, I think it's changing.
But yeah, I think it's just fundamentally like so unfair and it's meant to protect consumers
where, you know, the idea is if you have assets, you're smarter than everybody else or whatever.
I mean, of course, rich people are the smartest.
So I think, you know, like, I have a lot of people I think acknowledge that it has to
change and has to repress that the SEC crypto's favorite commissioner has been a big, big advocate
of that.
Yeah, it's like an other thing, like, let's just get it done.
So absolutely.
I mean, I think this is something that really needs to change in, you know, 10 years ago,
really.
Yesterday is just how do we make sure that Americans have the access to instruments that
will help them build wealth?
Because we're really seeing, you know, this stagnation in wages, we're seeing, you know,
it's really hard for Gen X millennials and Gen Z to own properties.
So like, what is going to be the solution here if all of these other routes to making
money and building wealth are now too expensive for young people?
What's the plan here?
And can it please be better than investing in Pepecoin?
Yeah.
Yeah, for sure.
And I think also like if you talk to the average crypto investor, like they know a lot
of stuff like they understand a lot about what they're doing and yeah, like they're gambling
or whatever, but I think a lot of people in this industry are extremely educated about
what they're doing.
And you kind of have to be though, right?
Yeah.
It's like, it's not easy to get into crypto, like I feel like there's so many, that's
kind of, ironically, one of the benefits of there being so many steps to being able to
like buying the crypto and then putting it into your hardware wallet and like all of this,
right?
So it requires you to do a little bit of research, but yeah, by that same token, it's keeping
other people out who either just listen to the bad news or are not willing to do all
those steps.
Yeah.
100%.
And yeah, I think to your point, like one, when I first started working and actually
had money for the first time in my life, I tried to set up an account at Schwab, I think,
and they wouldn't let me do it because they had, they were like, well, we'll only open
up an account if you can deposit X amount of money.
And I was like, I can't just invest like $500 in the stock market.
This is why Robinhood has really changed the game in a lot of ways.
I used to work at a digital broker called Drive Wealth where they powered investing for
like cash app and a bunch of other, these like digital wallets.
So I think that there's certainly like a renaissance going on in like equities brokerage and things
like that.
And it needs to happen more in crypto.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
So why don't we finish off with a quick lightning round, quick hits, ready to be struck.
Yes.
Okay.
Fable, favorite stable coin, single collateral die BTC price at the end of 2025.
Let's go with a cool million love the sound of that.
And are we looking at another DeFi summer?
Yeah.
I mean, every summer is DeFi summer now.
So for sure.
Well, thank you so much, Megan, for being here with us.
Where can our audience find you to follow for more tips and tricks and more payroll insights?
Yeah, for sure.
Follow us at @FranklinPayroll on Twitter.